Please implement a program that carries out a simulated recursive War tournament, logs detailed tournament play, keeps statistics about the tournament, and crowns a winner.

Your program should read in the names of tournament participants from a file, and write out the results of every step of the tournament into a log file with a very specific format. Both the Player File (the input file) and the Log File (the output file) will be specified as command line arguments to your program. That is, the code will be executed as follows:

war.exe ‹player_file› ‹log_file›

The Player File will be the name of a file containing participants, one per line. You should count the participants and ensure that the number of them is a power of two (2, 4, 8, 16, etc.). If not, your program should print an appropriate and informative error message, and exit.
For example, a valid Player File might look like this:

Jane
John
Mark
Alice
George
Susan
Frank
Betty
Upon reading a valid Player File, your program should then carry out a tournament among the participants named in that file. The program should create and write the results into the Log File with entries formatted exactly as in Lab 5, with one very small change as described below. (Again, capital letters, indenting, spaces, colons, etc., all matter): 

===
Jane VS. John
   Battle 1: Jane (JD) defeated John (2H): Jane 27, John 25
   Battle 2: John (AC) defeated Jane (5S): Jane 26, John 26
   ...
   Battle 21: John (5C) defeated Jane (2S): Jane 33, John 19
   Battle 22: John (4H) tied Jane (4C)
   War 1: Jane (QC) defeated John (10D): Jane 38, John 14
   ...
   Battle 120: Jane (KH) defeated John (QD): Jane 52, John 0
Jane (1) DEFEATED John in 120 Battles and 13 Wars
===
Mark VS. Alice
...
Mark (1) DEFEATED Alice in 392 Battles and 23 Wars
===


...
Jane VS. Susan...Jane (3) DEFEATED Susan in 429 Battles and 26 Wars
===
On a "results line" (e.g. "Jane (3) DEFEATED..." ), the number in parentheses indicates the number of games of war the player has won. (Note that this win total refers to the number of games of war that the player has won---where she/he accumulated all the cards in the deck---not the number of battles or wars won within a single game of war.)

In addition to the Log File, the program should print on the screen (i.e. cout), some statistics about the tournament. In particular, this information should include the following:

The winner of the tournament
The average number of battles per matchup
The largest number of battles in any one matchup
The biggest comeback (i.e. the fewest number of cards that a player had before coming back to win her matchup)